http://www.mainlineflatpacks.co.uk/pages/privacy-policy

Free Shipping
orders over £75 (ex VAT)
View cart
Boxes
Lil P&S (Peel & Seal)
Pizza Style Peel & Seal
No P&S (Requires Tape)
Filter All
Pizza Style Boxes (0427)
Cardboard boxes (0201)
Boxes
Lil P&S (Peel & Seal)
Lil P&S (Peel & Seal)
Pizza Style Peel & Seal
No P&S (Requires Tape)
No P&S (Requires Tape)
Filter All
Pizza Style Boxes (0427)
Cardboard boxes (0201)
Data subject’s rights
If you are located in the European Economic Area, in accordance with GDPR data protection regulations, you have certain rights with respect to your personal data. You have the right to request access to your personal data and to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal data by logging into your account or by reaching us using the contact information provided below. Furthermore, if you believe that we have unlawfully processed your personal data, you have the right to submit a complaint to the contact information provided below, or to your respective data protection supervisory authority. If you are the Customer of a Merchant, please contact the Merchant to exercise your data subject’s rights stated above.
Information security
We seek to use reasonable organisational, technical, and administrative measures to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of personal data. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system is guaranteed to be 100% secure, therefore we cannot guarantee absolute security of information. We encourage you to take care of the personal data in your possession that you process online and set strong passwords for your Lil Packaging account, limit access of your computer and browser by signing out after you have finished your session, and avoid providing us with any sensitive information whose disclosure you believe could cause you substantial harm.
All of Lil Packaging’s authorised personnel involved in the processing of your personal data have committed themselves to confidentiality obligations and shall not access or otherwise process your personal data without your authorisation if it’s not for the purposes of providing you with our Services.
In the event that we experience a data breach, we will notify you in compliance with the obligations set out in applicable laws.
International transfers of data
All the information you provide may be transferred or accessed by Lil Packaging, its affiliated companies and subsidiaries around the world for the provision of our Services as described in this Privacy Policy. When we transfer your information globally we will take necessary measures to ensure adequate protection of your information.
Lead forms via Social Media
Enquiries sent through forms generated by platforms such as Facebook and Linkedin will be sent directly to a sales specialist, you will not be opted in to any marketing activity unless you grant us permission to do so or are already an opted in member of our lists.
Should you choose to opt in to our newsletter and future communications such as catalogue mail outs and promotional offers – we will send you an email to confirm your application. Individual sign up to our marketing activity is double-opted in by default .
For each visitor to our website, our web server recognises no information regarding the domain or e-mail address. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, fax number, no information on consumers who browse our web page.
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.
We will not provide email addresses to any other parties.
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information you requested, unless you opted in during the time of contact.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events only if they have opted in. If you wish to opt out of receiving such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.
With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. If our information practices change at any point in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and we will only apply the new uses to data collected from the time of the policy change. If you are concerned about how your information is used please contact us by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.
Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address, or logging in to your account and choosing to unsubscribe – please note, you will only be contacted if you opted in. Upon request we can provide site visitors with access to their transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g. name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them.
Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. Customers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.
Privacy Policy changes
We may occasionally amend this Privacy Policy, for example in cases when we introduce new services or new features. The amendments to this Privacy Policy enter into force and are applied from the moment they have been uploaded to this page.
Therefore, we encourage you to check this page from time to time. By continuing to use our Services or otherwise providing personal data to us, after the amendments to this policy have been implemented, you agree to the updated terms of Privacy Policy.
Delivery Terms & Conditions
Returns Policy
Terms of Sale
Cookie Policy
Privacy Policy
FSC® certified
Copyright © 2020 Lil Packaging.
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
